{
    "id": "18cdb3df12ac4d318fc326a25adbff66",
    "title": "Idioms Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Soon the gloves were ........................... and they started screaming at each other.",
            "description": "When the gloves are off, people start fighting in a more hostile way. ",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They work hand in ...............................",
            "description": "When people work hand in glove, they work in close cooperation.",
            "answers": [
                "hand",
                "glove",
                "glue"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was dressed to the ............................... and made her friends jealous of her looks.",
            "description": "When you are dressed to the nines, you wear very smart clothes.",
            "answers": [
                "tens",
                "nines",
                "eights"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He can spend money like water. His parents have ...................................... pockets.",
            "description": "To have deep pockets is to be very rich.",
            "answers": [
                "rich",
                "deep",
                "large"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "To keep something under your ................................. is to keep it secret.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nose",
                "hat",
                "coat"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "That jacket is too large. You should find one that fits like a ..................................",
            "description": "If something fits like a glove, it fits perfectly.",
            "answers": [
                "coat",
                "hat",
                "glove"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I have a few tricks up my ................................... should he take action against me.",
            "description": "A trick up your sleeve is a secret plan or idea.",
            "answers": [
                "sleeve",
                "shirt",
                "collar"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am sure he will fail the test, but if he passes, I will eat my ..............................",
            "description": "This is an expression used to suggest that something is not going to happen.",
            "answers": [
                "hat",
                "shoe",
                "cap"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "When I started out I knew nothing about acting and I was just ……………………….. by the seat of my pants.",
            "description": "To fly by the seat of your pants is to rely on your instinct because you have no experience.",
            "answers": [
                "running",
                "jumping",
                "flying"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I must leave now. I have bigger .............................. to fry.",
            "description": "To have bigger fish to fry is to have more important things to do.",
            "answers": [
                "eggs",
                "fish",
                "chickens"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My uncle used to drink like a ................................ so we were not surprised when he developed liver trouble.",
            "description": "To drink like a fish is to have a problem with alcohol.",
            "answers": [
                "fish",
                "shark",
                "dolphin"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "When she started talking about her ex-boyfriends, he looked like a ........................................ out of water.",
            "description": "To be a fish out of water is to struggle in an unfamiliar or uncomfortable environment.",
            "answers": [
                "fish",
                "frog",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}